

HOLGER ZERBE

WEB DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

Full stack web developer with a focus on problem solving and experience in tutoring.

Several years of professional experience in customer care, which makes it particularly possible for me to communicate with customers and to implement their requirements in detail.

SKILLS

- HTML, CSS, Javascript ES6, PHP7
- React, Bootstrap, Laravel
- node.JS, Express
- mongoDB, mySQL

PROJECTS

holgerzerbe.github.io/portfolio

Portfolio

www.foodata.info

Final project at DCI

Web Application to scan a food barcode and get

information about food value

LANGUAGES

German: native language

English: B2 level

CONTACT

Place of residence: 12349 Berlin Email: holger.zerbe@web.de Phone: +49 30 92 25 40 41 Mobile: +49 170 610 95 30

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/holger-zerbe
XING: www.xing.com/profile/Holger_Zerbe2/cv
GitHub: https://github.com/HolgerZerbe

WORK EXPERIENCE

ANNE HAKER DENTIST

Internship Medical Office Manager | since February 2020

DCI DIGITAL CAREER INSTITUTE GGMBH

Tutor Web Developement | 2019 - 2020 Tutoring of HTML, CSS, Javascript (ES6), NodeJS, React

SELF-EMPLOYED ONLINE RETAILER

"Spielzeug-Preusse Holger Zerbe" - toys industry | 2011 - 2019 Product presentation, strategic purchasing, active trade fair visits, accounting and office management

SELF-EMPLOYED MARKET RETAILER

Market dealer with several ranges | 1998 - 2011

TIWO-WERKZEUGE GMBH

Executive Partner | 1995 - 1998

Tool wholesale with a commercial employee

TIMMERMANN & WOLF GMBH

Commercial employee | 1992 - 1995

Order processing, customer communication / complaint management, purchasing, calculation, inventory management

Student assistant | 1988 - 1992

Accounting, order processing, delivery driver

EDUCATION

FUTURE TRAINING & CONSULTING GMBH

PHP7 / Laravel course | Oct. 2020 - Jan. 2021

DCI DIGITAL CAREER INSTITUTE GGMBH

1 year web development course, modular system with practical orientation | 2018 - 2020

Completion March 2020 / repeated due to illness

TU BERLIN

Studied business mathematics | 1988 - 1991

ERNST-ABBE-GYMNASIUM, BERLIN

Graduation from high school (Abitur) | 1988